<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>xinyu wang</title>
    <description>hi, my name is xinyu. I&#39;m a designer in training. I&#39;m also a lover of art, music and tea.
</description>
    <link>http://xinyu0.github.io/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://xinyu0.github.io/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2015 16:12:10 -0600</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2015 16:12:10 -0600</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v2.4.0</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>Group lecture</title>
        <description>
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2015 08:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
        <link>http://xinyu0.github.io/iron_yard/2015/02/12/grouplecture.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://xinyu0.github.io/iron_yard/2015/02/12/grouplecture.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>iron_yard</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Learning grids &amp; practicing sketching</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;After 2 weeks of dabbling with Html Css, playing with Codepen, ITerm, github, and doing all sorts of coding stuff, this week we kind of switched gear and started talking about grids, and how they were used on the web. Of course, before this week’s lecture, even though I know that the layout of a website wasn’t just a random choice, I wasn’t very aware of grids, and didn’t know how they were used. Learning that you can chop up a web page into 10 columns, 12 columns is very interesting, and now I know in the future I can have a system to apply when designing the layout rather than just lining things up based on my intuition. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Grids are good. Learning it vs. actually putting it into use are 2 different things. Luckily, we don’t have to design some layouts right away. Our homework assignments were to sketch on paper a few pre-exisitng websites. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am very much excited to work on this assignment. I like to draw since I was a kid, despite most of my sketches are ugly. Also, due to lacking of ideas, I haven’t been doing it for many years. It feels good to sketch again. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I spent an average of 40 to 60 minutes per sketch, and yes, it’s not easy to draw a straight line. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://xinyu0.github.io/images/2015_02_11/IMG_20150211_224658.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Mashable&quot; /&gt;  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;2.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://xinyu0.github.io/images/2015_02_11/IMG_20150211_224707.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Penguin Books&quot; /&gt;  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://xinyu0.github.io/images/2015_02_11/IMG_20150211_224716.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;The New York Times&quot; /&gt;  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://xinyu0.github.io/images/2015_02_11/IMG_20150211_224724.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Medium&quot; /&gt;  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://xinyu0.github.io/images/2015_02_11/IMG_20150211_224733.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Roomba Product Page on Amazon&quot; /&gt;  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://xinyu0.github.io/images/2015_02_11/IMG_20150211_224742.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Fuzzco’s ‘what we do’ page&quot; /&gt;  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://xinyu0.github.io/images/2015_02_11/IMG_20150211_224749.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Art of the Menu&quot; /&gt;  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://xinyu0.github.io/images/2015_02_11/IMG_20150211_224757.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Your own Github Profile Page&quot; /&gt;  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://xinyu0.github.io/images/2015_02_11/IMG_20150211_224803.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Nest Thermostat&quot; /&gt;  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://xinyu0.github.io/images/2015_02_11/IMG_20150211_224816.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Time Magazine&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2015 14:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
        <link>http://xinyu0.github.io/iron_yard/2015/02/11/sketching.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://xinyu0.github.io/iron_yard/2015/02/11/sketching.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>iron_yard</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Reflections on the first 2 weeks of my web design class @the iron yard</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;It has already been 2 weeks into my web design class @the iron yard, and it’s crazy how fast time files. It’s like going back to school, but it’s not like school. I really enjoyed being a student again, and I kind of don’t want to graduate in 10 weeks :) because learning is fun~  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I have done quite a bit over the last 2 weeks. So far, I have learned the basics of HTML, CSS, the terminal, github, etc. Looking back, with no doubt, I feel really happy with how much I’ve learned and done, and Sam is one of the best teachers I ever had, as she knows so much in both design and tech (2 of my favorite things). I’m getting better at picking up new stuff, but I’m still struggling. One of the great things about learning @tiy is that I know I’m not going through this alone. Everyone here is so nice and so willing to help. And if you are like me, you are shy and don’t like to talk. That’s totally fine. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That being said, even though I’ve learned a lot, I can’t stop thinking in 10 weeks I will actually graduate and go out on my own as a designer. It seems really scary. It feels like trying to grow a baby to an adult in 3 months (This actually what I picture in my head!) Anyway, this has been a great journey so far for me, and I am so glad to be here with my fellow classmates and be able to learn and challenge myself again. &lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2015 08:22:47 -0600</pubDate>
        <link>http://xinyu0.github.io/iron_yard/2015/02/10/iron_yard_week1_and_week2.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://xinyu0.github.io/iron_yard/2015/02/10/iron_yard_week1_and_week2.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>iron_yard</category>
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
