<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>xinyu wang</title>
    <description>I&#39;m a Web &amp; UI designer currently located in Austin, TX.
</description>
    <link>http://xinyudesign.com/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://xinyudesign.com/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Tue, 05 May 2015 14:28:31 -0500</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 05 May 2015 14:28:31 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v2.4.0</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>my long story</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;I didn’t want to be a designer or an artist when I was growing up. I made drawings and paintings but thought I was not good enough to make it as a living.   &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I went to college in Las Vegas for business and after college, I followed the typical path. I started working because I needed a job and because I thought that was what I was supposed to do. I did not quite know what kind of job I wanted after college, so I started working at a big hotel company there. I thought it was just something that’s going to be temporary. But while working at that job, I can never figure out what I wanted to do, so I kept working at the same job. As months pass, as years pass, I still didn’t know, and it got more and more frustrating. After a while I started to hate my job. I felt dread when going to work. After work, I will come home, being tired, emotionally drained, and just frustrated with everything in my life. But what was even harder was I didn’t know what else I wanted to do or capable of doing. I went on-line, explored different careers, trying to find something that I will enjoy doing but nothing looked appeal to me. so I just kept working there. This went on for about 3 years. It was a tough time in my life. I remembered that I was getting many grey hairs because of the stress. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I was always interested in starting an on-line business, because I spent so much time on-line ever since when I was in high school. I had read many stories about people making money on-line, and they had so much freedom because they can work anywhere they wanted. and it was around 2012 when I read “The $100 Startup” by Chris Guillebeau and “4-Hour Work Week” by Tim ferris, and reading them just changed my attitude about life. I decided I didn’t want to work work work until 65 and then retire and then enjoy life. I wanted enjoy life now while I was still young. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In 2014, I decided to go to the World Domination Summit in Portland, Oregon because I needed to get away, I needed to do something different. My plan was when I went back to Las Vegas, I was going to quit my job. But when I was at WDS, I never found out what it was I wanted to do. So when I came back to Las Vegas, I didn’t have any other options. So I went back to work, and that was really depressing. I stuck with it for another 5 months. During that time, I started going to local meetups. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Finally around September 2014, I decided to make a serious change, because I just did not like what I was doing or not doing with my life. It was the time in my life I just had enough. I remembered I drove home one night after work. I was mentally tired. I was just staring at the road. I was thinking “I am so tired. I wanted to do something I enjoyed.” but I had just been not taking much actions for a long time. So I came home that night, turned on my laptop, I opened up a word document, and typed a list of things I needed to do. I didn’t want to put it off any more. I always wanted to learn photoshop, but I had always put it off, because I had always focused on making money. but this time, it was about doing something I enjoyed. I want to do something that will allow me to be creative, allow me to draw. I started reading about people going to bootcamps or workshops. before that, I had looked at books, I looked at online tutorials but I didn’t have the time and the patience to learn how to do it. So i put my dream aside. but this time, I found an instructor named Sam Kapila. I came across her podcasts, one of her podcast I believe was recorded when she was teaching at university. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I decided to move to Austin.I was going to study web design. This has been something I wanted to do. But for one reason or another, I put it off. So in Dec 2014, I went over to Austin. The school was going to be for three month. I wasn’t sure if I was going to like it. I was so used to be in my comfort zone. This is so far away from my comfort zone. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I started living in Austin. I started going to school. I actually enjoyed being a student again. I enjoyed studying, working on projects. It was so nice to wake up and not worry about going to work. I enjoyed talking to other students, eating great food in Austin. My plan was to start doing some web design freelancing.  &lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 30 Apr 2015 16:57:39 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://xinyudesign.com/2015/04/30/more_about_me.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://xinyudesign.com/2015/04/30/more_about_me.html</guid>
        
        <category>thoughts</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
